{
    "id": "f417c78dbe2540c49300beded49dc6a3",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The turban and the beard easily distinguish a Sikh ——————— others.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The laboratory should be furnished ———————- all necessary equipment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is keen ———————- building a career in music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a disgrace ——————- her family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was the first to alight ——————- the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "down",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is busy ——————– his studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is addicted ——————– drugs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "from",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The hotel is adjacent ——————- the railway station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "During his speech, he alluded ——————– a story in the Vedas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize ——————— him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The inspector commented favorably ——————– our work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I congratulated him —————— his success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}